(birds chirping)
(Nobara Kugisaki groaning)
[Nobara Kugisaki]
Couldn't they put in
a few more vending machines?
[Megumi Fushiguro] They can't.
There are only so many workers
allowed to come onto the campus.
Hey.
Where are the first-years?
Errands.
[Toge Inumaki] Bonito flakes.
Are they safe?
[Toge Inumaki] Salmon.
They can handle an errand run.
They're not three years old.
No, that's not what I'm saying.
I'm saying today's the day
Kyoto's principal comes here,
to go over the plans for
the Exchange Event, right?
[Toge Inumaki] Tuna.
[Panda] Satoru's fighting
with the Higher-Ups
because they arranged
for the first-years
to get dispatched on that
Special Grade case, right?
And Kyoto's principal is one
of those Higher-Ups, isn't he?
So, if the two of them
run into each other...
Look, the first-year
they were targeting,
Itadori, is dead.
I doubt the principal plans
to do anything to the other two.
Plus, it'll be in
broad daylight.
The old man from Kyoto
won't wanna make a scene.
[Toge Inumaki] Salmon.
[Panda] An instructor might have
his position to worry about,
but that's not the
case for students.
You mean Mai is coming?
Speak up.
I'm only guessing.
Students aren't usually
invited to these meetings.
But still,
they do seem to love
harassing us, don't they?
Both Toudou and Mai.
Mai Zenin?
I'm surprised to see you.
What are you doing here?
Oh, another one?
They do look alike.
Are they sisters?
[Megumi Fushiguro]
Yes, they're twins.
Don't call me a twin, Fushiguro.
You make it sound as
if Maki were my equal.
You ought to just call me Mai.
So these two are subs for
Okkotsu and the third-years?
We came along with the principal
because we were
worried about you.
Your classmate died, we heard.
Was that rough,
or did it not affect
you that much?
(both grunting)
What are you trying to say?
Hey, it's all right.
Some things are
hard to admit out loud,
so let me say it for you.
Calling him a vessel
makes it sound nice,
but the truth is he was
a half-Curse monster.
Having that tainted
inhuman being beside you
who was brazenly calling
himself a Jujutsu Sorcerer
must've been revolting, right?
So aren't you feeling
better now that he's dead?
(Megumi Fushiguro grumbling)
(Nobara Kugisaki grumbling)
Mai, why do you always
have to stir things up?
I'm only here for one thing,
to see if these guys are
fit to take Okkotsu's place.
That's all I wanna know.
(Megumi Fushiguro grunts)
Fushiguro, was it?
What kinda woman's your type?
[Both] Hmm?
-(intense music) -If I
don't like your answer,
I may beat you half
to death right here,
and after that,
drag Okkotsu, or at
least the third-years,
out to the Exchange
Event, suspended or not!
Oh, and by the way,
my type of woman's a tall
one with a big gorgeous ass!
(Opening Theme Music)
(singing in Japanese)
(birds chirping)
Why would I wanna
discuss my taste in women,
especially with you,
a guy I just met?
Hmm?
That's true. This guy's
seriously anti-social.
You're not helping me.
Please don't talk and
make this any harder
than it already is.
Kyoto third-year Aoi Toudou!
Introduction over!
Now we're friends, so hurry
up and answer my question.
If you prefer men,
that's fine too.
A person's fetishes reveal
everything about him.
People with boring
taste in women
are boring people themselves,
and there is nothing I hate
more than a man I find boring.
The Exchange Event is
where my soul can be free
as the blood boils
and the flesh clashes.
Who knows what I'll do
if my last Exchange Event
ends up only boring me.
Last? Can't he compete
as a fourth-year too?
The Event's just for
third-years and under.
Oh.
[Aoi Toudou] I'm already
cutting you too much slack
by offering to beat
you only half to death.
Now answer me, Fushiguro,
what kind of woman is your type?
What is this, a comedy act?
So what's with your outfit?
That your summer uniform?
Weird, but it's not bad.
[Megumi Fushiguro]
Kugisaki's unarmed.
I'll have to go along with
this to avoid a confrontation.
Not forgiving people
isn't such a bad thing.
It just goes along
with your kindness.
I don't really have a type.
As long as one's
character is unshakeable,
there's nothing
more I can ask for.
Mm-hmm.
That's not a bad answer.
If you had said big boobs,
I would've had to kill you.
Shut up.
(sniffling) I knew it.
You really are
boring, Fushiguro.
(Megumi Fushiguro gasps)
(both grunting)
[Megumi Fushiguro] Ah!
(gasps) Fushiguro!
Oh well,
there goes poor Fushiguro.
(Nobara Kugisaki grunts)
Even a talented Second
Grade Jujutsu Sorcerer
is nothing more
than a first-year
when he's up against
the top-grade Aoi Toudou.
I'll have to go and
comfort him later, huh?
I thought you and Maki
were identical, but you're not.
Maki's a hundred times
prettier than you are.
[Mai Zenin] Hmm?
Trouble sleeping?
You've got open pores.
(grunts) Maybe I
should teach you
-(pistol cocks)
-(Nobara Kugisaki gasps)
how to speak to others.
(dramatic music)
(Megumi Fushiguro grunting)
I knew it as soon as
I saw you, Fushiguro.
I could tell you'd turn
out to be a boring guy.
But then, you should
never judge a person
just by their looks,
isn't that right?
So I went out of my way
to ask you the question,
but you've just
trampled on my kindness.
Your head looks like a pineapple
and you're about
as smart as one too.
Wait, Toudou.
That Toudou?
The who defended
against last year's
unprecedented
jujutsu terror attack
by the Curse User Geto,
during The Night Parade
of a Hundred Demons?
And when the
parade came to Kyoto,
he exorcised a Special Grade
and five First Grade
Cursed Spirits by himself.
That Toudou?
Still, there are some
First Grade Sorcerers
capable of beating
a Special Grade.
What's shocking is
I heard.
You don't use Cursed Techniques.
Huh? Oh, no, that rumor's false.
I did against the Special Grade.
He doesn't use them
against First Grades?
Is he a monster?
That's good to know.
Nue
plus Gama!
(intense music)
(toad croaks)
Bottomless Well!
(toads croaking)
(Aoi Toudou grunts)
I'm up against a hardcore
close-range fighter.
I'll keep my distance
and restrain him.
(Aoi Toudou grunts)
(toad croaks)
He's fast,
so he wasn't at
full speed earlier.
[Aoi Toudou] You're
flimsy and shallow.
Both your body
and your taste in women!
(Aoi Toudou grunts)
(Megumi Fushiguro grunting)
-(Megumi Fushiguro groaning)
-(Aoi Toudou grunting)
(both grunting)
(Aoi Toudou laughing)
(Megumi Fushiguro groans)
[Megumi Fushiguro]
Damn it. His power is insane!
(Megumi Fushiguro groans)
(Aoi Toudou grunts)
(both grunting)
(Megumi Fushiguro groaning)
Just wait.
I'm not finished with you!
-(Aoi Toudou yelling)
-(Megumi Fushiguro groaning)
(intense music)
You're always just so boring!
(Aoi Toudou grunting)
Are you even trying to fight?
You're acting so proud,
but I've been holding back.
Fine then, if you insist,
then I'll show you.
Huh?
(laughing) Okay, bring it!
[Toge Inumaki] Don't move!
(Aoi Toudou laughing)
(Aoi Toudou groaning)
What the hell are you two doing?
Whew, just barely safe.
[Toge Inumaki] Bonito flakes.
(Megumi Fushiguro exhales)
Okay, I guess that
might be an out.
(spits) Long time no see, Panda.
[Panda] Why
couldn't you just wait
until the Exchange Event?
Now go on home, or
I'll start screaming no!
You don't have to
tell me to go home.
Now where'd I put my jacket?
At least after this,
it looks like I might not
be bored the whole time.
Give Okkotsu a message.
Tell him he had better show up.
What a jerk.
I merely panda. No
understand human speak.
[Toge Inumaki] Salmon.
[Mai Zenin] If you wanna
continue as a Jujutsu Sorcerer,
you better watch who
you pick a fight with.
(Mai Zenin giggles)
(Mai Zenin gasps)
Just what do you
think you're doing
to our errand runner, Mai?
Ah.
You're such a loser I didn't
even notice you come in, Maki.
If I'm a loser then
you must be one too.
All you can do is imbue
objects with Cursed Energy,
and you've got shit
for Cursed Techniques.
Better than no
Cursed Energy at all.
My neck gets so sore looking
up at others all the time,
so I need you, dear
sister, to look down on.
[Maki Zenin] Ah, give it a rest.
We're both at rock
bottom and equally pathetic.
Nobara, can you stand up?
No way.
She won't be
getting up for a while.
I hurt her pretty good.
(Mai Zenin gasps)
What's this? A challenge?
(both grunting)
Nice support, Maki!
You put a bunch of holes
in my brand new tracksuit.
I oughta rip this rag off you
and use it to make it
my own summer uniform.
Next time I'll put the
holes in your body instead.
Plus, you can't wear this
with those stick
legs of (groans).
[Nobara Kugisaki]
Just shut your mouth.
[Aoi Toudou] Come
on, Mai, we're leaving.
[Nobara Kugisaki] What? No way.
Oh, there's my jacket.
Where's Fushiguro?
Don't worry, he's fine.
He's out with the others.
Looks like you're having fun.
(panting) I am,
but I'm just
getting started here.
No, you're not.
Unlike you, I still have
important business
to attend to here in Tokyo.
My personal handshake
and it's with Takada!
[All] Huh?
Who knows what I might
do if I don't catch that train
and I can't make it
to the hall on time.
Come on, Mai, let's go.
[Mai Zenin] (grunts)
You're so selfish.
[Aoi Toudou] I still can't
believe I lost the lottery
for the one in Kyoto.
As for you,
you won't get off this
easy at the Exchange Event.
Quit acting like you
beat me, damn it,
and gimme that uniform now!
Cut it out, you idiot.
Winning or losing a fight
here doesn't mean a thing.
Save that up for
the Exchange Event.
Maki, is Mai right?
She said you don't
have Cursed Energy.
Yes, that's true.
In fact,
I need these to even see Curses.
That's why I use Cursed Tools.
They already have
Curses imbued in them.
I can't pour my own
Cursed Energy into them
to do things like you all do.
Oh.
Like that thing
Gojo gave Itadori.
Then why be a Jujutsu Sorcerer?
To spite my family.
I can't wait to see their faces
when I become a
bigshot sorcerer.
After all, they've looked
down on me all these years.
Come on.
Let's hurry over and see Shoko.
[Nobara Kugisaki] You know,
I really respect you, Maki.
[Maki Zenin] Is that so?
(upbeat theme music)
(river babbling)
(birds chirping)
Why is Yaga still not here?
Time is a precious thing
to an old man who's
coming ever closer to death.
[Satoru Gojo] I'm
sorry, but Principal Yaga
won't be here for a while yet.
Oh?
Somehow, the schedule
he was given was incorrect.
After some threats to Ijichi.
Thank you for the other
day, Principal Gakuganji.
Sorry? What day
are you referring to?
Don't play dumb
with me, old man.
I'm talking about Yuji Itadori.
As head of the conservatives
you were involved too, right?
My goodness.
Youth these days.
Have you no manners anymore?
Have you lost all
respect for your elders?
I never had any respect
for you to start with.
Elders like you love
to act important
and frankly it just sucks.
[Kasumi Miwa] Watch it!
[Satoru Gojo] Hm?
Your conduct is unacceptable.
Stop it, or I'll report you
to the proper authorities.
Oh, wow!
It's Satoru Gojo in-person
sitting right in front of me!
Knock yourself out.
I don't plan to
chat for very long.
(Kasumi Miwa grumbling)
[Kasumi Miwa] (giggling) He
spoke to me, he spoke to me!
[Satoru Gojo] Last
night, I was attacked
by two unregistered
Special Grade Cursed Spirits.
Oh?
Well, that is very unfortunate.
Don't get me wrong here.
It was about as much trouble
as answering a sidewalk survey.
[Kasumi Miwa] (moaning) So cool!
These two Cursed Spirits
were capable of communication,
and they probably have
allies who are just as strong.
And it's not just our foes.
Hakari, Okkotsu,
and your Toudou.
In recent years, the
quality level of our students
has risen dramatically as well.
Then there was last year's
incident with Suguru Geto.
And now, the appearance
of Sukuna's vessel.
What are you trying to say?
You're still not getting this?
The wave of power you guys
have been trying to hold back
with your pointless
status and traditions
has grown bigger
than you can handle
and is now descending upon us.
You won't be able to
measure the coming age
with just the classification
of Special Grade.
And if you really believe
I'm the only one
who's gonna fight back,
you're gonna wind
up hurt, old man.
I think
that you're way out
of line, young man.
Oh, I'm scared.
Well, I've said all I wanted
to say, so I'll be going now.
(Kasumi Miwa grumbles)
Oh, and Principal
Yaga will be along
in a couple of hours.
Later!
[Kasumi Miwa] A couple of hours?
(Yoshinobu Gakuganji sighs)
Miwa, would you
find me some tea?
Yes.
I'll be right back.
(Kasumi Miwa giggling)
If I can catch up to him,
maybe I can get him to
take a picture with me!
-(bright music)
-(crowd chattering)
Taka-tan Beam,
if you don't mind.
Awe! I'm happy to!
Tan, Taka-tan!
-(Aoi Toudou gasping)
-(crowd chattering)
[Worker] Time's up, pal.
(serene piano music)
Excuse me.
Did you do that
inside the theater?
(Mahito chuckles)
Wow,
so you can actually see me.
(ominous music)
(rain pouring)
It's a gruesome sight.
Are you ready to
witness it, Itadori?
(Yuji Itadori grunts)
(Closing Theme Music)
(singing in Japanese)
[Kasumi Miwa] (giggling)
Thank you so much!
[Satoru Gojo] Oh,
it's my pleasure.
[Kasumi Miwa] (giggling)
I got a photo with him!
My tea?
(Kasumi Miwa gasps)
[Announcers] Juju Stroll!
(crowd chattering)
[Fan] Man, she's hot,
but she's staring at
us like we're garbage.
[Fan] Stop looking at her!
Mai, sorry to be so long.
What's wrong?
Did something happen
while I was gone?
[Mai Zenin] Aside
from having to come
to this stupid event?
[Aoi Toudou] So this
moment has finally come.
Huh?
What's this?
[Aoi Toudou] For the
next handshake event.
You should go experience how
wonderful Takada is in-person.
[Mai Zenin] This is
just plain annoying.
[Aoi Toudou] This
is my duty as a fan,
and as her future husband.
[Mai Zenin] And
that's just plain creepy,
but if I reject his offer,
he'll just get even
more annoying.
What's the matter?
-(high-spirited music)
-(crowd chattering)
(detector beeping)
Oh. Yeah, sure.
(worker gasping)
[Takada] Wow, a girl!
Is this your first time
coming to see me?
Yeah.
[Takada] What's your name?
[Mai Zenin] Mai.
[Takada] (giggling)
Mai, are you tired?
Did you have to
wait in line long?
[Mai Zenin] It was more the
people than the line really.
Then come back again
when you're feeling better.
I won't forget you ever, Mai.
[Aoi Toudou] Ah,
Mai, you're back.
How was it?
[Mai Zenin] Fine.
Yeah, I get it.
Takada is the kind of woman
who's difficult to
describe in mere words.
[Mai Zenin] (inhales)
She's not bad. (sighs)
(upbeat theme music)